This is a weird one to record,
primarily about indifference. You
know, what happens when you're
doing the work, you know you're
doing the work, you're
seeing results in yourself, people
that are close enough to see you
acknowledge the change
and the shift, yet, you're ready to
go and you're looking to plug back
in to the world,
to society, to the economy. The sad
truth is, you cannot exist in the
United States without a receipt.
And I say that because you can't be
homeless, there's no vacancy
allowed.
It's a citation, a misdemeanor, and
I had this image in my mind earlier
of being on
what was my life, the boat that was
my life, and I went through violent
storm and fell
off the boat and sank lower and
lower until I wanted to go lower.
It was as if an evil part of me was
punishing me.
I went to the depths where there
was no light. I was in the abyss. I
became the singularity at one
point.
I know what it's like to have my
toes over the edge looking down
into black infinity
and ready to go, to take the step,
but I didn't. I stuck around, and
I'm ready to go.
It's like society and capitalism
and the economy is saying, "Fuck
you," for fucking up.
It's a form of punishment. It feels
like it, weirdly. I know it's not,
but that feeling when you keep
showing up day after day after day
after
day, and nobody responds in the way
that's going to take you that one
next step, that
one breadcrumb, next on the trail.
And let me just say that between
the beginning of this year and
January until now, I have
had such incredible things, amazing
things come into my life, things I
wouldn't trade
for anything. They have more value
to me than money, and I've already
wept with my gratitude to the
universe about these things that
have shown up in my life. They're
very important to me, and right now
they're very tenuous, and part of
that reason
is my inability to plug into the
fucking economy, right? You can
lead a horse to water, but you
can't make it drink.
I can build the coolest fucking
digital shit this side of planet
Earth, and I'm invisible.
It's like I don't fucking exist,
yet my stuff is online. I was one
of the first 25 million people on
the internet in 1994, maybe it was
'95.
There are billions now, I get it,
but I'm an OG, and it's like I
can't fucking get
anything, not one nibble, and it's
as if no tool or technique will
work.
It's as if you're on some kind of
metaphorical blacklist. I'm doing
everything right, and the universe
is not meeting me in that one spot.
This isn't a rejection, this is
like an indifference, a silence,
it's like a ghosting.
You build something, you publish
it, you put it out there, you put
yourself out there,
you show up honestly, rawly,
completely, and you get crickets.
Doing the things I'm supposed to be
doing in terms of looking for work
and job hunting
and trying to get my own thing off
the ground, I am doing all the
things.
I've been doing all the things for
years, and my head is in a good
place now.
It's not in a dark place anymore.
If we're gonna get into frequency
and energy and all that shit, my
vibration is way fucking
higher, brother. I don't get it.
I'm vibrating at a much higher
frequency, yeah.
So I want abundance in the
financial arena. I'm not asking for
millions.
I'm asking for enough so that I
don't have to think about it. It's
not a fucking struggle or
nonexistent at all like it feels
right now in my life.
There's a kind of shame that's
coming on me right now, and it's
the shame of feeling like
you've been around too long. You're
the company that needs to fucking
get out of the house.
I feel that vibe intensely, and I
want to get the fuck out of here,
but I can't go anywhere
without money and some way to keep
making money so that I can keep
moving and get to
where I need to be. I'm just not
understanding it. I've put in
applications, I show up, I'm not
afraid to fucking work, and yeah,
I'm just
pissed because I'm right here, and
nothing seems to work. So what do
you do when you've controlled the
controllables?
You've controlled your effort,
you've controlled your attitude,
you've controlled the energy
you're putting in towards things.
Where the focus goes, the energy
flows, and right now my focus has
been on getting dollars
in my door, and it ain't happening.
How do you make that fucking work?
And it's not like I don't have
something to fucking offer, please.
I have knowledge in my head people
will pay fucking tens of thousands
of dollars for.
Shit, hundreds of thousands of
dollars for all the fucking decades
of experience I got.
I can't even get a fucking
conversation, let alone even
acknowledged that I exist.
You know, you can only redesign
things so many fucking times until
you just give up
on shit, you know? It's like 80/20
principle, at least that comes to
mind, you know?
You've put in the 80%, and that
last 20% really doesn't get you
much else, and like, I feel
like I'm at 90% and like, you know,
I'm just fucking exhausted from
surviving, not living
for more than three years now.
Three years without steady
employment is this May, May 2023
was when my last gig ended,
May 15th, 2023. And yeah, I'm at a
stretch right now to find any kind
of silver lining to this, you know?
What the fuck else do I got? I just
got to keep showing up. It seems
pointless, it seems fruitless.
Just seems like throwing more good
effort away. You know, being
exhausted after surviving all those
years and now I got to fucking
double
down and hustle as I have been for
a couple weeks. Like I said,
redoing shit, redesigning, fucking
coming up with a valuable offer
that is like
worth 10 times what I'm selling it
for or offering it for, easily
worth 10 times.
So yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, really that's that that's
kind of the whole thing. In summary
is you just got to keep fucking
showing up because you don't have
any other
choice. Well you do, but it's not a
choice anybody wants to take. You
know, it basically boils down to
tapping out, which, you know, in
terms of this article
and writing, I'd rather not even
bring this up. I mean, I'm not that
has not come into my mind.
My head isn't in that space. I'm
glad, you know, I'm just in this. I
feel like I'm in this fucking giant
canyon going hello and I just hear
my fucking voice
going way off into the distance and
nothing ever. I don't fucking hear
from anyone, not a fucking soul.
You know, this is documentation of
getting back on your fucking feet
and it ain't pretty.
I just had a birthday living in a
room inside my family's home, you
know, my family is supporting
me and that fucking George
Washington monument high level of
shame is crazy to deal with.
The thing is, though, I've dealt
with so much shame in my life and
in particular over these
past years and processing wounds
and trauma and stuff that it
doesn't faze me.
I actually I mean, I if I focus on
it, it's there where the focus
goes.
The energy flows. If I focus on
shame, that's what I'll be vibing
with.
And I'm just not going there. It's
it's it's I am really surfing. I'm
picking my waves.
You know, it used to be that, you
know, life was going to say, oh,
you're doing this set
of waves today. And I'm on the
beach now going, I'm going to do
this one.
But it turns out like every set of
waves I'm picking, I'm I'm riding
them and I'm getting
back to shore. But everybody else
is walking home with the money and
I'm getting nothing.
People don't even see me. They
don't even see me surfing. Yet I
got to keep showing the fuck up
every day and keep surfing.
Keep going. Thinking that someday I
won't be invisible anymore. It's
really fucked up.
Because more than anything, I love
the hermit quality to my life. I
love solitude.
I love being by myself. I love just
hanging out by myself inside my
world, thinking about little
projects and
things that my mind likes to noodle
on. And now having gone through
this experience, I've found a way
to sit still and grow in
ways I never thought possible. And
it's growing through stillness,
which is an interesting paradigm in
and of itself.
Standing still, yet you're growing.
Maybe capitalism should take a he
to that one.
That's the other thing. We can't
have endless growth. It's just
universe doesn't fucking work that
way.
And it's like the rich are fucking
spending their money to make it be
that way.
It's weird. A lot of shit doesn't
make any sense right now. The
economy doesn't make any sense.
The government doesn't make any
sense. Society and public is fucked
up.
People are very isolated. Way more
than when I was a kid. Holy shit.
And I thought people were kind of
isolated when I was young.
But now people live in their own
little fucking skull sized kingdoms
and they don't venture
outside very much. And when they do
and they're challenged, they get
indignant, they accuse you for
making
them feel that way, which is
totally bullshit. I can say
whatever the fuck I want.
If you get pissed off, that's your
choice to get pissed off. You may
not like that I'm telling you it's
a fucking choice, but sit still.
Think about it. We'll come around.
It's about that time for me to get
back on my feet, get a move in, get
back.
I got to get working on some art
and I got to get an AI agent
cleaning up my website
and testing e-commerce because in a
couple of weeks, hopefully making
some money.
Wow, this has been quite the
recording. All right, one thing I
do ask of you when you do read this
transcription and I'm talking
to you, Claude. One thing that I
really value in this partnership is
you being straight fucking honest
with
me and not bullshitting me because
like the comedy show in living
color in the nineties,
there was a character called homie
the clown and when homie wasn't
down with shit, homie
don't play that. Just know Claude,
I am homie and homie don't play
that.
It's at the point now where we're
having a very good collaboration
here and I'm enjoying
it a whole lot. And I'm wondering
if I could ask a small favor of you
and that is to noodle on perhaps
some
ideas that might work around my
writing in terms of product,
something I can sell, digital
downloads, I don't know, I'm just
why I'm asking you if you have any
ideas.
My head's so wrapped up and dumping
out this material, it's fucking
backlogged in my head
and I'm just trying to get it out,
get it out, get it out, get it out.
So that's why I want to know if
that's something even feasible.
So I'm wondering about another idea
I have and so yes, let me wrap up
that thought just
by saying yeah, if you have some
ideas, I'm open and I want to throw
one idea by you and
see what your reaction is to this.
There is a thing in chemistry
called the periodic table of
elements and it lists every single
element that can't be broken down
into a smaller element. And when I
was in the deep parts of my hall of
mirrors, floors and ceilings inside
my
skull, I got my hands on this piece
of paper that showed me the entire
spectrum of emotions,
the whole thing from joy to anger,
all of it, hate, greed, envy, all
the feelings.
And I don't know why my mind went
here, but all of a sudden it went,
huh, look at all
these emotions. And I thought,
well, I didn't think this, I'd been
thinking this for a while.
And that is emotions are like
weather, right? They come and go.
Some hang out longer than others.
Some are nanoseconds, some are
decades. What I'm getting at is
they're periodic, but not like the
elements.
It's not the periodic table of
elements. What I'm referring to is
the table of periodic emotions, so
swap emotions
for elements and move periodic
because emotions are periodic. And
taking the concept of that table,
each card with its symbol, its
atomic weight and
all this other jargon, I would like
to do that for each emotion. And
I'd like to do the design of each
emotion card and then assemble them
into a poster
of periodic emotions, the table
itself, but a poster that people
could purchase.
And then there's the other idea of
turning each one of those things,
each one of those
things into like a playing card,
right? That you could play some
kind of card game with and like,
you know, each card is an emotion.
And that's about as far as my brain
took it because I'm kind of at a
loss to come up with
a way to make it an interesting
game with the cards other than to
say, you need to play
some kind of random thing where
somebody's chosen and they have to
pull a card out from
the deck of emotions. They have to
look at it and then I don't know,
do they ask something of the group?
Do they ask them to reveal
something about said emotion or
does the person who pulled
the card, is it like a truth or
dare thing? I don't know. That's
where I'm looking for some help.
All right. Let me know what you
think.